翻译、整理：baki
我要去洗手间
I need to go to the bathroom.
我得去厕所
Tengo que ir al baño.
听着，我要撒尿，好吗？
Listen, I got to piss, okay?
你想让我尿裤子吗？
You want me to piss my fucking pants?
我快尿裤子了，好吗？
I'm about to piss my fucking pants, all right?
我靠
Fuck me.
你说这地是你的
You say you own this land.
我们拥有使用权
We have the rights.
不
No.
这块地是我们的
We own this land.
你拥有地表，
You own the surface,
是你从丹尼尔·皮尔索尔那里买来的，
which you purchased from Daniel Piersall,
丹尼尔·皮尔索尔的父亲
and Daniel Piersall's father
在1993年把矿产权
sold the mineral rights in 1993
卖给了二叠纪盆地信托公司，
to the Permian Basin Trust,
他们又把开采权转包给了
梅里迪安石油公司，
who subcontracted the rights to Meridian Oil,
这家公司被康菲石油收购了，
which was bought by Conoco Phillips,
然后卖给了M-TEX石油公司，
and sold to M-TEX Oil,
他们最近才发现了这些权利
who only recently discovered the rights.
我们不希望你们的石油公司来这里
We don't want your oil here.
好吧，一只手许愿，另一只手拉屎，
Well, wish in one hand, shit in the other,
看看哪个先满
see which one fills up first.
也许我会把你从蛋蛋到喉咙切开
Maybe I slice you from your huevos to your throat
然后把你挂在桥上
and hang you from a bridge.
嗯？
Huh?
看看石油公司还会不会来
See if oil companies come then.
好吧，首先他们会雇哈里伯顿公司
Well, first they'll hire,Halliburton to build files
给你们这些混蛋建档，
on you fucking assholes
这是联邦调查局做梦都想拥有的
that the FBI only dreams about having.
然后他们会派30名一级特战队员
Then they'll send,30 Tier 1 operators
从三叶公司过来
像打彩罐一样把你们干掉
from Triple Canopy, and they'll bust you like a fucking piñata.
如果你们这些笨蛋真的逃回了墨西哥，
And if any of you dipshits do make it back to Mexico,
他们会用无人机炸毁你们的房子
they'll blow your fucking house up with a drone.
连同你们的家人一起
With your family in it.
建一口新井要花六百万美元
It costs six million to put in a new well.
他们他妈的要在这里建800口
They're putting in 800 right fucking here.
那就是48亿美元的抽油机
That's 4.8 billion in pumpjacks.
他们还会再投入10亿美元
They'll put in another billion
用于水、住房和货运
on water and housing and trucking.
每桶78美元，那就是每天640万美元
At $78 a barrel, that's 6.4 million a day.
在接下来的50年里
For the next 50 fucking years.
所以，是的，石油公司会来的
So, yeah, the oil company's coming.
所以，他们派你来告诉我们滚蛋？
So, they send you to tell us fuck off?
他们派我来协商土地租赁事宜
They sent me to negotiate a surface lease.
我们会给你们修一条
漂亮的全天候道路，
And we'll build you a nice all-weather road
通往我们的油井和高速公路
that leads to our oil wells and to the highway.
如果你们需要，还可以修几条其他的
And a few others, if you need them.
他要给我们修路
He's gonna build us a road.
嘿，事情是这样的，
Hey, here's the deal,
而且只有这么办：
and it's the only deal:
你们别碰我们的生意
我们也不碰你们的
You don't fuck with our product, we don't fuck with yours.
因为如果你们敢，我们就在街对面
Because if you do, we'll put in a DEA substation
建一个缉毒局分局
right across the fucking street.
成交吗？
We got a deal?
成交
We got a deal.
土地租赁协议在这里
Surface lease agreement's in there.
需要签字的页数都做了标记
Signature pages are marked.
现在，我们需要一个地址
用于支付土地租赁费
Now, we'll need an address for the surface lease payment
和损害赔偿金
and the damage reimbursements.
损害？
Damage?
是的
Yeah.
我们会赔偿你们土地的损失，
We'll pay you for the damage to the land
因为我们为了修路和建抽油机平台
占用了你们的土地
we built your roads on and the pads for our pumpjacks.
你付钱给我？
You pay me?
是的，我们付钱给你
Yeah, we pay you.
嗯，奇怪的生意
Mm, strange business.
跟你们的生意一样
Same as yours.
不，我不这么认为
No, I don't think so.
你们销售一种产品，
You sell a product
而你们的客户都依赖这种产品
that your customers are dependent on.
是的
Yes.
这都一样
It's the same.
我们的规模更大而已
Ours is just bigger.
我们走吧 （西班牙语）
Vámonos.
石油和天然气行业每天
Oil and Gas Industry makes
能获得30亿美元的纯利润
$3 billion dollars a day in pure profit.
每年能产生超过4.3万亿美元的收入
Generates over $4.3 trillion dollars a year in revenue.
它是世界第七大产业，
It is the seventh largest industry in the world,
排名高于食品生产、
ranked ahead of food production,
汽车生产、煤矿开采，
automobile production, coal mining,
而制药行业只有1.4万亿美元，
and at 1.4 trillion, the pharmaceutical industry
甚至没有进入前十名
doesn't even crack the top ten.
排在石油和天然气行业
之前的那些行业
The industries listed ahead of oil and gas
完全依赖于
are completely dependent on
石油和天然气
oil and gas.
他们发展得越多，
The more they grow,
我们就发展得越多
the more we grow.
这就是规模
That's the scale.
这就是这件事的体量
That's the size of this thing.
而且规模越来越大
And it's only getting bigger.
这该死的活儿
This fucking job.
但在赚到这些钱之前，
But before any of that money is made,
你得先拿到租约
you gotta get the lease.
你得确保获得开采权，锁定地表
You gotta secure the rights and lock up the surface.
然后还要照看业主，照看工人们
Then babysit the owners, babysit the crews.
然后还要应付警察和媒体
Then manage the police and the press
当那些家伙们闹事的时候
when the babies refuse to be sat.
这就是我的工作
That's my job.
搞定租约，然后管理人员
Secure the lease, then manage the people.
第一部分很简单
First part's pretty simple.
是第二部分会让你送命
It's the second part that can get you killed.
什么--
What the--
快点
Come on.
你是诺里斯宝贝？
You baby Norris?
- 库珀  - 不
- Cooper. - Nah.
我觉得宝贝更好
I think baby's better.
上车
Get in.
♪ "No Vacancy" by Treaty Oak Revival ♪
三杯黑咖啡？
Three black coffees?
哦，还有一位
Oh, you got another one in there.
你想要点什么，甜心？
You want something, sugar?
呃...
Uh...
我确实有这种效果
I can have that effect.
你喜欢黑咖啡，
Do you like black coffee,
还是加点牛奶？
or a little bit of milk in there?
我要，呃...
I'll take, uh...
是的，其实加点牛奶  我要一杯拿铁
Yeah, actually some milk. Can I have a latte?
- 什么鬼？！一杯什么？
- What the fuck?! A what?
你竟然点了一杯该死的拿铁？什么？
You just order a fucking latte? What?
一个贵族  - 什么？
An aristocrat. - What?
通常要等到银行家们
起床了才做拿铁
Don't normally make lattes till the bankers wake up.
我们没时间等一杯该死的拿铁
We don't have time to wait for a fucking latte.
你他妈的为什么需要一杯拿铁，兄弟？
Why the fuck do you need a latte, bro?
- 我只是点了-- - 他让她做
- I-- I just ordered-- - He's asking her to make
- 最复杂的东西，伙计
- 我们得去工作了
- the most complicated shit, man. - We got to get to work.
- 对不起  -“对不起 ”
- Sorry. -"Sorry."
你想再要一份欧式早餐吗？
You want to ask for a continental breakfast?
- 我-- - 你他妈的有什么毛病？
- I-- - What the fuck is your problem?
- 哦，又来了  - 又来了
- Oh, here we go. - Here it comes.
这白小子点了一杯拿铁！
The white kid ordered a latte!
干得好，伙计 第一天
Great job, man. First day.
一共27，甜心
That'll be 27, sweetie.
难以置信
Unreal.
这是给你的，亲爱的
This is for you, darling.
♪ 她说她会在八点半左右给我打电话 ♪
♪ Said she'll call me round half past eight ♪
♪ 真是漫长的一天，别熬夜太晚…… ♪
♪ Been a damn long day, don't wait up too late... ♪
嘿，如果你要在油田工作，
Hey, if you're gonna work the patch
你就得学会喝黑咖啡，
you got to learn how to drink it black,
因为我们做的每件事都得抓紧时间
'cause everything we do is on the fucking go.
我只是不喜欢它的味道
I just don't like the way it tastes.
跟味道无关，孩子，这是为了补充能量
Ain't about the taste, son, it's about the fuel.
六个小时后，当你需要提神的时候，
Six hours from now when you need a jolt,
你不能喝那种凝固的牛奶
you can't drink that curdled milk.
你会吐得我的卡车到处都是
Be throwing up all over my truck.
你不会想吐在他的卡车里的
You don't want to throw up in his truck.
事实上，把那个给我
In fact, give me that.
是的，把那玩意儿——
Yeah, give that shit--
你父亲说要把你培养成一个石油工人
Your father said to make you into a roughneck.
不妨现在就开始
May as well start now.
♪ 世界颠倒了 ♪
♪ Well, the world is on its head ♪
♪ 我感谢我的幸运星，我还活着 ♪
♪ And I thank my lucky stars that I ain't dead ♪
♪ 我一生都在负债 ♪
♪ I spend my whole life in the red ♪
♪ 我尽我所能养活我的家人 ♪
♪ And I done my best to keep my family fed ♪
♪ 所以当我放下我的重担时 ♪
♪ So when I lay my burdens down ♪
♪ 不要想着我的债务 ♪
♪ Keep my debts out of your mind ♪
♪ 就一会儿 ♪
♪ Just for a while ♪
♪ 我所有的烦恼和考验 ♪
♪ All my troubles and my trials ♪
♪ 它们散落在路上 ♪
♪ They lay scattered on the trail ♪
♪ 好几英里…… ♪
♪ For miles and miles... ♪
好吧，星期一，看看你有什么本事
All right, Monday, let's see what you got.
♪ 我一生都在付出 ♪
♪ I been paying my whole life ♪
♪ 努力想找到我所有痛苦的根源 ♪
♪ Trying hard to find the blame for all my strife ♪
♪ 我一直在挥霍我的支票 ♪
♪ I been burning through my check ♪
♪ 我从未感受到脖子上的黄金…… ♪
♪ And I never felt the gold around my neck... ♪
- 昨晚过得怎么样？
- How was the night?
人力资源部——
他们停下来询问帮派关系
H.R.-- they stopped to ask for gang affiliations.
所以现在我的钻井队一半是血帮，
So now I got this drilling crew that's half Bloods,
一半是瘸帮，他们决定...
half Crips, who decided to have a gunfight
昨晚在该死的营地里来一场枪战
in the fucking man camp last night.
你不能戴草帽 现在还不是复活节
You can't wear straw. It ain't Easter yet.
今天会有95度
It's gonna be 95 today.
我觉得这复活节过得够可以了
你们觉得呢？
I'd say that's Easter enough, wouldn't you?
该死的，戴尔
Goddamn it, Dale.
我要告诉你多少次
How many times am I gonna have to tell you
把豆子倒进该死的碗里？
to pour the beans in a fucking bowl?
你一周烧坏一个微波炉
You burn up a microwave a week
就因为把那些该死的罐头放进去
putting them fucking cans in there.
- 在碗里的味道不一样 - 不，没有
- Tastes different in a bowl. - No, they don't.
它们尝起来完全一样
They taste exactly the fucking same.
嗯，味道不一样
Mm-mm, taste different.
好吧，我猜牛仔文化
Well, shit, I guess cowboy culture
对你们俩来说已经见鬼去了，是吧？
is out the fucking window with you two, huh?
你要是看到这屋里有个牛仔，你就指出来
You see a cowboy in this room, you point him out.
你的任务什么时候完成？
When's your hitch done?
- 今天 嗯 谢天谢地
- Today. Mm. Thank God.
- 11点到法院 - 好的
- Be at the courthouse by 11:00. - Yeah.
- 不是11点半，是11点
- Not 11:30, 11:00.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
喂？
Hello?
- 什么？
- What?
什么？ - 多-多远？
What? - How-how far?
把定位发给我
Just send me a pin.
我正在路上 好的
I'm on the way. All right.
去哪的路上？
On your way where?
你明天得来给我做证词
You're gonna have to depose me tomorrow.
今天必须完成，汤米
It has to be today, Tommy.
这些狗娘养的都缠着我，
These sons of bitches are so far up my ass,
他们都盯着我的扁桃体了
they're staring at the back of my tonsils.
好吧，那只能明天了，
Well, it's gonna have to be tomorrow,
因为我想我找到我们的飞机了
'cause I think I found our plane.
你们把飞机弄丢了？
You guys lost a plane?
你们他妈的是怎么把飞机弄丢的？
How the fuck you lose a plane?
……价格与全国平均水平持平，
...prices are up with the national average,
达到3.86美元
reaching $3.86.
瓦莱罗和特索罗炼油厂的维护工作消息
News of maintenance work at both Valero and Tesoro
计划于5月进行，这引发了人们对
refineries scheduled for May has sparked fears of
夏季汽油短缺的担忧
a summer gasoline shortage.
是啊，问问他们为什么
在五月份进行维护，凯特
Yeah, ask 'em why they're doing maintenance in May, Kate.
欧佩克下周开会讨论增加产量的问题
OPEC meets next week to discuss an increase in production.
不，他们不会
No, they're not.
他们会减产的，亲爱的
They're gonna cut production, honey.
他们会把石油价格抬到一百美元
They're gonna take oil to a hundred.
你的消息来源是谁啊，这么不靠谱？
Who the hell is your shitty source, anyway?
尽管一些业内人士担心减产……
Although some insiders fear a cut in production...
凯特真是聪明
Well, look at the brain on Kate.
你应该继续听你那些线人的话
You keep listening to your insiders.
你可能会弄明白这场游戏
You may figure this game out.
这他妈的到底是怎么回事？
What in the fucking hell?
给内特打电话
Call Nate.
是我们的飞机吗？
Is it our plane?
是的，看起来像是
Yeah, it looks like it.
- 它在哪儿？
- 在我们修建的皮尤特油田旁的路上，
- Where is it? - In about a thousand pieces
摔成了一千块碎片
out here on the road we built by the Pyote field.
- 嘿，我得挂了再打给你
- 我应该给沃斯堡打电话吗？
- Hey, let me call you back. - Should I call Fort Worth?
是的，应该有人打
Yeah, somebody should.
真是乱七八糟
Quite a mess.
你还没见识到真正的乱七八糟呢
You ain't seen the mess yet.
我可以把我的卡车留在这里吗？
Can I leave my truck here?
- 这是你的路
- It's your road.
联邦航空管理局说你报告这架飞机被盗了
FAA says you reported this plane stolen.
是的，六周前
Yeah, six weeks ago.
你没觉得需要向我报告吗？
And you didn't feel like you needed to report that to me?
好吧，如果你是他妈的飞机警察，
Well, if you were the fucking airplane police,
我就会报告，沃尔特，但你不是，
I would have, Walt, but since you're not,
所以我报给了飞机警察
I called the airplane police.
通知你是他们的工作，不是我的
It's their job to call you, not mine.
好吧，他们没有
Well, they didn't.
我不知道该说什么
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
这就是联邦政府的办事效率
That's the federal government for you.
这些都是什么？
What's all this?
飞机失踪后你应该
立即打电话给我的75个理由之一
One of 75 reasons you should have called me
就在飞机失踪的那一刻
the second that plane went missing.
- 可卡因？ - 也许吧
- Cocaine? - Maybe.
也许是海洛因
Maybe heroin.
飞行员在哪儿？
Where's the pilot?
在驾驶舱里烤焦了
Cooking in the cockpit.
我让缉毒局和联邦航空局
派危险物品处理小组
I got DEA and FAA sending HAZMAT crews
过来把他弄出来
down here to pull him out.
离那些东西远点，站在上风处
Stay upwind of that shit.
那玩意儿比子弹杀人还快
It'll kill you quicker than a bullet.
那是一辆TTP公司的卡车
That's a TTP truck.
是的
Yep.
这辆破卡车在我们路上干什么？
What the fuck's it doing on our road?
他可能也要问你，那架飞机在干什么
He's probably gonna ask you the same thing about that plane.
你有没有向你的保险公司
报告飞机被盗？
Did you report it stolen to your insurance company?
你知道这些破事是怎么回事
You know how this shit works.
卡车、挖掘机，各种各样的东西
Trucks and excavators and all kinds of shit
每天都会丢失
go missing every day.
几个月后，它们又回来了
And then a couple months later, they find their way back.
如果我举报这里所有被偷的东西，
If I reported everything that was stolen around here,
整个该死的二叠纪盆地都会变成犯罪现场
the whole fucking Permian Basin would be a crime scene.
该死的
Goddamn it.
我每天要从这里运走4200桶石油
I got 4,200 barrels of oil
我每天都要把这些运出去
I got to move out of here every day.
不能走这条路
Not on this road.
暂时不行
Not for a while.
沃尔特，这件事我需要你帮帮忙
I'm gonna need some love on this deal, Walt.
帮什么忙？
What kind of love?
那种可以把警方报告日期改早的忙
The kind that backdates a police report.
看在上帝的份上，汤米
For God sakes, Tommy.
联邦航空管理局是知情的
The FAA was aware.
他们搞砸了
They dropped the ball.
就用我给他们的日期，
Just use the date that I gave them,
然后匹配一下，就这样
and match it, that's all.
你知道有多少双眼睛盯着这件事吗？
You know how many eyes are gonna be on this thing?
那些车牌上带“G”字的
The kind with a "G" on their license plate.
我不会把日期改早的
I ain't backdating nothing.
好吧，在今天的报告中，
Okay, in today's report,
注明上个月已通知联邦航空管理局
just note that FAA was notified last month.
你能做到吗？
Can you do that?
这是事实，沃尔特
It's the fucking truth, Walt.
我会写进我的报告里
I'll put it in my report.
好的，请全部用大写字母
All right, in all caps, please.
嘿，我需要一个道路施工队来这里
Hey, I'm gonna need a road crew out here.
我会给你发个定位
I'm gonna drop you a pin.
需要在事故现场周围绕行半英里
Need a half a mile detour around an incident site.
嘿，沃尔特，我们能不能在那一边
Hey, Walt, can we build a road
建一条绕行路，
around on that side over there,
这样我们就可以绕过这堆破事了？
so we can elbow around this shit?
- 在那边？ - 是的
- Over there? - Yeah.
在那边，尸体和毒品所在的地方？不行
Over there where the dead body and the drugs are? No.
好吧，那边怎么样？
Okay, well, how about that side over there?
那边有尸体和毒品吗？
Is there any dead bodies and dope over there?
还没看过那边
Haven't looked over there yet.
那我们他妈的去看看怎么样？
Well, how about we fucking go look then?
妈的
Shit.
好吧，我这边没看到毒贩的尸体
Well, I don't see any dead drug dealers over here.
这里没有尸体，也没有毒品--
Not any dead guys here, not any dope--
操
Fuck.
沃尔特？
Walt?
这里有个死人
There's a dead son of a bitch over here.
- 喂！先生？
- Yo! Sir?
- 去把它用胶带封起来 嘿，我回来了
- Come tape it off. Hey, I'm back.
听着，我们需要足够铺一英里的钙质土
Listen, we're gonna need enough caliche for about a mile
才能绕过这该死的烂摊子
to get us around this fucking mess.
所以，我希望你马上开始
直到完成为止，不要停
So I want you to start right now and don't stop till you're done.
让他们整夜跑
Run 'em all night.
好的
All right.
这周我可不想干你的活
I wouldn't want to have your job this week.
该死，沃尔特，哪一周我都不想干你的活
Shit, you wouldn't want to have my job any week, Walt.
打电话给蒙蒂·米勒
Call Monty Miller.
太好了
Great.
好吧，看来今天一整天都是星期一了
Well, it looks like it's gonna be Monday all day today.
实际上，汤米，今天不会是星期一
Actually, it won't be Monday once today, Tommy.
今天是星期五
It's Friday.
不可能是星期五 我昨天才到这儿
It can't be Friday. I just got here yesterday.
3月1日，你就改成周五到周二了
March first, you switched to a Friday through Tuesday.
如果你看看我，你就会看到日历
If you would look at me, you would see the calendar.
如果你看看我，我们还会是夫妻
If you looked at me, we'd still be married.
好吧，我正以每小时80英里
的速度在高速公路上行驶
Well, I'm going down the highway at 80 miles an hour.
如果我看着你，我可能会死
If I looked at you, I'd probably die.
那辆卡车真够大的，不是吗？
That was a pretty big truck, wasn't it?
好吧，今天是星期五
Okay, it's Friday.
你有安斯利
You have Ainsley.
- 安斯利？ - 是的，这周末是你的
- Ainsley? - Yeah, it's your weekend.
你刚才还告诉我
我的周末是周三和周四
You just told me my weekend is Wednesday and Thursday.
你的周末是，但世界上其他人
Yours is, but the rest of the world
都在周六和周日休息
takes Saturday and Sunday off.
那个世界包括我和你的女儿
That world includes me and your daughter.
维克多和我要去卡波
Victor and I are going to Cabo
我不能把安斯利一个人留在家里
and I can't leave Ainsley alone in this house.
亲爱的，她都17岁了
Honey, she's 17 fucking years old.
你见过她新交的男朋友吗？
Have you seen her new boyfriend?
该死的 等等，我靠边停车
Goddamn it. Hold on, I'm pulling over.
看看这孩子
Look at this kid.
我的意思是，她光看照片就能怀孕
I mean, she could get pregnant from the fucking photograph.
好吧，我明白你的意思了
Okay, I see your point.
你相信她开车来找你吗？
Do you trust her driving to you?
去敖德萨？
To Odessa?
- 是的  - 你在跟我开玩笑吗？
- Yeah. - Are you shittin' me?
让她去米查姆
Have her go to Meacham.
我会让她和工程师们一起坐飞机
I'll put her on the flight with the engineers.
好吧……
Okay...
你换了发色
You changed your hair color.
是啊，红发实验结束了
Yeah, the redhead experiment is over.
嗯，我一直更喜欢你的自然发色，
Well, I always preferred your natural color,
说实话
to tell you the truth.
宝贝，你从来没见过我的自然发色
Baby, you've never seen my natural color.
那么你和弗农什么时候去……
So what time are you and Vernon going to--
- 维克多  - 维克多
- Victor. - Victor.
呃，你们什么时候出发去卡波？
Uh, what time are y'all leaving for Cabo?
今晚才走
Not till tonight.
那你早上8点为什么要穿成这样？
Well, how come you'd be dressed that way
那时候？
at 8:00 in the morning, then?
你觉得这算盛装打扮？
You think this is dressed up?
呃，是的，我觉得是 你也这么觉得
Uh, yeah, I do. And so do you.
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
是的，我喜欢
Yes, I do like it.
你看，人生一大乐趣
You see, one of life's great pleasures
就是让你看看你错过了什么
is showing you what you're missing.
不用给我看我也知道，亲爱的
You don't have to show me to know, honey.
我已经知道了
I already know.
我们的宝贝怎么样？
How's our baby?
呃，这是他第一天上班
Uh, it's his first day.
第一天都不容易
First days ain't easy.
又一个诺里斯家的进了油田
Another Norris in the oil patch.
真是浪费
What a waste.
不是我的主意
Wasn't my idea.
苹果落地离树不远，不是吗？
Apple don't fall far, does it?
你也是这棵树的一半，亲爱的，别忘了
Well, you're half of the tree, in case you forgot, darlin'.
总之，下午3点前把她送到机场，
Anyway, just get her at the airport there
好吗？
by 3:00, all right?
不然就他妈的挂我电话，随便你
Or fuckin' hang up on me, either way.
我是这样开始的，
The way I got started in this,
我当时在西德克萨斯州做石油工程师
I was working in West Texas as a petroleum engineer
我决定是时候
and I decided that it was time
去经历一些人生冒险了
to have a little adventure in life.
我回应了一则特别的广告
And I answered this one particular advertisement
去利比亚的一家公司工作
to go to work for a company in Libya
担任现场石油工程师
as a field petroleum engineer.
我的阿拉伯朋友过去常常嘲笑我
My Arabic friends used to laugh at me
因为我说阿拉伯语带着德州口音
because I would speak Arabic with a Texas accent.
他们很难听懂我的阿拉伯语，
And it was hard for them to understand my Arabic,
即使我说的是正确的词语
even though I was speaking the true words.
事情进展得很顺利，直到1967年
Things were going along pretty well until 1967.
当时发生了阿以战争
There was the Arab/Israeli War.
我们当然能看出阿拉伯人对
And we could certainly see that the Arab view
我们这些旅居海外者的看法
开始变得模糊
of us expatriates was beginning to dim.
我跟你说吧
I will tell you what.
我差不多要放弃在
20号州际公路以北找油了
I am about done with looking north of I-20.
上周我打了三口井
连水都没找到
I sunk three wells last week. I didn't even hit water.
那是因为20号州际公路以北根本没有水
It's because there ain't any water north of I-20.
比它南边还少
More than there is south of it.
哪个县？ - 石墙县
What county? - Stonewall.
该死，他们在那儿抽油都一百年了
Shit, they been sucking that oil for a hundred years.
把快干涸的井进行水力压裂，
Frack the ones that are going dry
然后赶紧撤
and get the hell out.
再说，你打三口井能干什么？
Besides, what are you gonna do with three wells?
- 我的矿产就在那儿
- That's where my minerals are.
你应该在新冠疫情之后买下盆地
Should've bought the basin after Covid hit.
不，我不玩那么大的
No, I don't play that big.
我们当时以五分之一的
价格买了一百个区块
We were buying 100 sections for five cents on the dollar.
那不算大，那叫聪明
That ain't big, that's smart.
在那片红色的岩石土壤里
找不到新油田了
There ain't no new oil to be found in that rocky red dirt.
- 该死 这可不是什么好事
- Shit. This ain't gonna be good.
等我一下，伙计们
Give me a second, boys.
好的，去吧，蒙蒂
Yeah, go ahead, Mon.
嘿，让我找个安静的地方
Hey, let me get somewhere quiet.
好了，情况有多糟？
All right, how bad?
这很难回答
That's a tricky one to answer.
是你和内特能处理的事情吗？
Is it something you and Nate can handle?
他们会从三个方向攻击你
Well, they're gonna hit you from three directions.
保险公司、受害者家属和TTP
The insurance company, victims' families and TTP.
好吧，我会处理TTP
All right, well, I'll handle TTP.
米德兰最好的诉讼律师事务所是哪家？
Who's the best litigation firm in Midland?
他们不会在这里提起诉讼
他们会在休斯顿提起诉讼
Well, they won't file here, they'll file in Houston.
第一个聘请谢泼德-哈斯廷斯
律师事务所的人会赢
First one to hire,Shepherd-Hastings wins.
你在那边看好谁？
Who do you like over there?
克莱·钱德勒是个杀手
你想让我给他打电话吗？
Clay Chandler is an assassin. You want me to call him?
不，我会打给他
你只要把这件事压下去，别让它上新闻
No, I'll call him, you just keep this shit out of the news.
这就是问题所在，蒙蒂
This is the patch, Monty.
一架装满毒品的飞机
An airplane full of drugs
被一辆油罐车碾过，这不算新闻，
being run over by an oil tanker ain't news,
这只是另一个星期一
that's just another Monday.
是啊，但今天不是星期一，汤米
Yeah, well, it ain't Monday, Tommy.
对我来说今天是星期一
It's Monday to me.
他应该检查什么？
What's he supposed to be checking?
塔克阀
Tucker valve.
塔克阀是什么鬼东西？
What the fuck is a Tucker valve?
第一天上班
First day on the job.
我操，我不能让汤米·诺里斯的儿子
Motherfucker, I can't have,Tommy Norris's son
死在我的地盘上——让他从那儿下来
dying on my pad-- get him down from there.
好的，我马上就去
All right, I'll do it right now.
你得一直爬到最上面！
You got to go right up at the top!
- 这样？
- Like that?
我没看到！
I don't see it!
你得再爬高点！
You got to go higher!
高点！
Higher!
我没看到任何阀门！
I don't see any valve!
我记得你对我做过这种事
I remember when you did this shit to me.
差点吓尿裤子
Almost shit my pants.
你确实吓尿裤子了
You did shit your pants.
高点！
Higher!
哦，操
Oh, fuck.
- 我没看到阀门！
- 没有？你没看到仪表吗？
- I don't see the valve! - No? You don't see the gauge?
没有！没有仪表！
No! No gauge!
哦，你知道吗？算了，它在这下面
Oh, you know what? Never mind, it's down here.
哦，搞什么鬼
Oh, what the fuck.
所以我可以下来了？
So I can come down?
什么，你想整天待在那里吗？
What, are you gonna stay up there all day?
快下来！
Gets your ass down here!
哦，糟了
Oh, shit.
哇！
Whoa!
- 哦，糟了  - 不——
- Oh, shit. - Nah--
这孩子要他妈的死了 嘿，孩子！
This kid is gonna fuckin' die. Hey, kid!
慢慢来！
Take your time!
快，快，快
Go, go, go, go, go.
糟了
Shit.
哦，操
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
- 他卡住了  - 他会没事的
- He's stuck. - He's gonna be fine.
嘿
Hey.
你为什么这么害怕，伙计？
Why you so scared, man?
你戴着安全带呢
You got a harness on.
你系着安全绳呢，好吗？
You're wired, all right?
是的
Yeah.
- 你还好吗？ - 嗯哼
- You good? - Uh-huh.
看着我
Look at me.
先把你的脚放好
Get your feet set first.
- 来吧
- Come on.
然后一只手，然后另一只手
Then one hand, then the other.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
三个接触点
Three points of contact.
- 三个接触点  - 是的，始终保持
- Three points of contact. - Yeah, yeah, at all times.
- 好的，好的  - 好吗？
- Okay, okay. - Okay?
我们下去吧
Let's head down.
- 好的  - 没时间了
- Okay. - Ain't got all day.
该死
Sh-Shit.
你很棒，伙计 就快到了
You're good, man. Almost there.
你还好吗？发生什么事了？
You good or what? what happened?
我去，兄弟 好了，走吧
Holy shit, bro. All right, let's go.
- 你这笨蛋 快点
- You dumbass. Come on.
让我看看你的手
Let me see that hand.
好的，冲洗一下
Okay, rinse it.
现场办公室里有急救箱
There's a first-aid kit in the field office.
包扎一下
Wrap it.
所以压力表一直都在这下面？
So the gauge was down here the whole time?
等一下，你们是不是在耍我？
Wait a minute, were you guys fuckin' with me?
是的 第一天，伙计 总会发生的
Yes. First day, man. Gonna happen.
- 是的 嘿，快点
- Yeah. Hey, come on.
继续！
Go on!
欢迎来到油田
Welcome to the patch.
你做得很好，孩子
You did good, son.
你做得很好
You did good.
♪ “永恒的爱人” - 49温彻斯特乐队 ♪
♪ "Everlasting Lover" by 49 Winchester ♪
♪ 永恒的爱人 ♪
♪ Everlasting lover ♪
♪ 我有很多话想对你说 ♪
♪ I got a lot,I want to say to you ♪
♪ 你让我感觉不再那么孤单 ♪
♪ Well, you make me feel less lonesome ♪
♪ 比以往任何时候都更不孤单 ♪
♪ Then I ever used to ♪
♪ 永恒的爱人 ♪
♪ Everlasting lover ♪
♪ 亲爱的，并非我想要这样 ♪
♪ Honey, it ain't that I want to ♪
♪ 但有时疼痛会占据我 ♪
♪ Oh, but sometimes the pain takes over ♪
♪ 我会悄悄溜走 ♪
♪ And I'll just slip through ♪
♪ 当我喝醉了，感觉被拒绝的时候 ♪
♪ When I get stoned and I feel rejected ♪
♪ 疲惫于路途，身心俱疲... ♪
♪ Weary from the road and half beaten down... ♪
你的一天是要开始还是结束？
Your day about to start or just end?
我的正在进行中
I'm in the middle of mine.
好吧，你想吃什么？早餐还是晚餐？
All right, which you want? Breakfast, supper?
你怎么没有午餐菜单？
How come you ain't got a lunch menu?
因为在油田没有午餐这回事
Because there ain't no such thing as lunch in the patch.
说得真对，艾莉
Truer words, Ellie.
- 晚餐  - 好的
- Dinner. - All right.
中间可以喝啤酒吗？
And can you drink beer in the middle?
我觉得没问题 对某些人来说今天是星期五
I don't see why not. It's Friday for somebody.
好吧，我给你拿一壶
All right, I'll bring you a pitcher.
谢谢
Thanks.
要来一壶吗？
Want to order a pitcher?
啊，已经点过了
Ah, already did.
如果你可以接受超醇的话
If Ultra's okay with you.
哦，米狮龙爱好者，啊？
Oh, a Michelob man, huh?
是的，两百万牛仔竞技爱好者总不会错
Yeah, well, two million team ropers can't be wrong.
我们得从这起火灾中拿到赔偿，汤米
We got to get paid on this fire deal, Tommy.
你烧了8000英亩地
You burned up 8,000 acres.
我们损失了30万美元
We're sitting on a $300,000 loss.
我什么都没烧 是大火烧的
I didn't burn up anything. The fire burned it.
起因是你们抽油机的开关故障
Started by a faulty switch in your pump jack.
然后被时速50英里的风刮起来了
And spread by,50-mile-an-hour winds.
这完全是“天灾”
It's got "act of God" written all over it.
如果不是因为那阵风，
If it hadn't been for that wind,
那东西蔓延不会超过50米
that thing don't spread past 50 meters.
听着，M-TEX一直是个好伙伴
Listen, M-TEX has been a good partner.
这就是我们没有加入集体诉讼的原因
That's why we didn't join that class action.
但我们确实遭受了损失，我们需要赔偿
But we suffered real damages and we need to be reimbursed.
伙计们
我们是来吃饭的还是来吵架的？
Boys, boys, boys. We eatin' or just arguin'?
- 现在只是在争论，亲爱的  好吧
- Just arguing now, honey. All right.
听着，如果我们赔偿表面损失，
Listen, if we pay for surface damages,
我们就等于承认了错误
we're admitting fault.
- 你们是错的  - 你们也是
- You are at fault. - Well, so are you.
火是从你们客户的地上烧起来的
It started on your client's land.
他们那里有消防队
And they got a fire crew over there.
他们没有阻止它
他们甚至都没有尝试
They didn't stop it, they didn't even try.
我们会签署保密协议
We'll sign an NDA.
因为它就值它印在纸上的那点价值？
'Cause that's worth the paper it's printed on?
听着，在解决这个问题之前
我们不会让你们再钻一口井
Listen, we will not let you drill another well
直到这件事得到处理
until this is handled.
好吧，这样如何：
Okay, how about this:
我付给你们30万美元
但这是太阳能租赁费
I pay you $300,000, but it's for a solar lease.
我们的客户不想在牧场上安装太阳能
Our client doesn't want solar on the ranch.
我们不卖太阳能电池板
我们是家该死的石油公司
We don't sell solar panels, we're a fucking oil company.
但我可以用太阳能或风能的
权利来解释这笔付款
But I can justify payment on solar rights or wind.
你说的是什么时间段？
What time period you talking about?
我TMD不在乎 就六个月吧
I don't give a shit. Make it six months.
我只是不想赔偿你们的损失
I just don't want to have to pay you damages.
我觉得我可以让这行得通
I think I can make that fly.
我看不出你有什么理由办不到
I don't see why you couldn't.
这比在男子监狱里卖淫还容易
That's easier than selling pussy at a men's prison.
我觉得这很冒犯，先生
I find that offensive, sir.
对谁来说，对卖淫的还是对囚犯？
To who, the pussy or the prisoners?
- 我觉得很难
- I find it difficult
和冒犯我的人做生意
to do business with people who offend me.
嗯，你看，我们之间没有生意往来
Well, you see, we're not in business together.
我们租用你们的矿产权，作为交换，
We lease your mineral rights, and in exchange for that,
我们每年支付你们250万美元
we pay you $2 and a half million dollars a year.
并且维护你们的道路，挖你们的蓄水池
And maintain your roads and dig your stock tanks.
所以，别自欺欺人地认为你是个农场主
So, don't delude yourself into thinking you're a rancher.
你是一个用我们给你的钱
养牛的石油商
You're an oilman who spends the money we give you on cattle.
如果不是我们，
If it hadn't been for us,
你家在50年代就失去那个牧场了
your family would have lost that ranch in the '50s.
所以，你只要说声“谢谢”
拿这30万美元的草场费，
So, you just say "Thank you," take the $300,000 for the grass,
然后我每个月继续
给你寄20万美元的支票
and then I keep sending you,$200,000 checks every month.
但你竟敢假装我冒犯了你
But don't you dare pretend that I offend you.
你应该笑着说：“我收下了 ”
You smile and say, "I'll take it."
很好的提议
Very good offer.
我建议你接受
I recommend you take it.
我接受，但我不会笑
I'll take it, but I ain't smiling.
我猜也是
I guess not.
得给张支票你才肯笑，是吧？
It takes a check to make you do that, don't it?
我等不及那一天了，
I can't wait for the day
就是你和所有像你一样的人
离开这里的那一天
when you and everyone like you leaves this place.
你最好仔细想想
You might want to think that through.
因为如果我走了
那就意味着石油没了，
'Cause if I'm gone, that means the oil's gone,
如果石油没了，那就意味着钱没了，
and if the oil's gone, that means the money's gone,
那就意味着你也要走了
and that means you're gone.
我们会写好合同，下周给你
We'll write it up, get it to you next week.
现在我们可以吃饭了吗？
Now are we eating?
我想我现在只能一个人吃了
I guess I'm eating alone now.
哦，宝贝 你想吃点什么？
Oh, baby. What can I get you?
爸爸！
Daddy!
宝贝  - 嗨！
Baby. - Hi!
你一天比一天漂亮，小天使
You get prettier every day, little angel.
你没把那些小瓶装的
蒂托斯酒喝光吧，
You didn't drink them out of those little Tito's bottles,
- 对吧？ - 爸爸，当然没有
- did you? - Daddy, of course not.
是你们的工程师喝的
Your engineers did that.
好吧，他们经验丰富
Well, they have the practice.
我想让你见见我的男朋友
I want you to meet my boyfriend.
你妈妈没说你男朋友要来啊
Your mother didn't say anything about the boyfriend coming.
因为你了解妈妈 她知道的越少越好
'Cause you know Mommy. The less she knows the better.
她就是个直升机父母
She's such a helicopter parent.
- 我不知道那是什么意思  - 就是盘旋
- I don't know what that means. - Just hovering
不停地盘旋，总是这样
and hovering and hovering, always.
爸爸，这位是达科塔
Daddy, meet Dakota.
诺里斯先生
Mr. Norris.
- 幸会，先生  - 是的，很高兴见到你
- Pleasure, sir. - Yeah, good to meet you.
达科塔？你姓什么？
Dakota? What's your last name?
洛文，先生
Loving, sir.
“达科塔·洛文 ”
"Dakota Loving."
你编不出这种鬼话
You can't make that shit up.
我们走吧
Let's go.
风真大
So windy.
♪ 我的拖车看起来像个酒铺 ♪
♪ Well, my trailer looks like a liquor store ♪
♪ 或者像个刚被打劫过的 ♪
♪ Or maybe one that just got robbed ♪
♪ 而且，嗯，我这里有你能想到的 ♪
♪ And, well, I've got every bottle ♪
♪ 各种酒，亲爱的... ♪
♪ You can think of, honey... ♪
那么，孩子们，你们今晚想做什么？
So, what would you kids like to do tonight?
嗯，你有车可以借我们吗？
Well, do you have a car we could borrow?
不，我没有
No, I don't.
这辆呢？
What about this one?
这辆是我的
This one's mine.
好吧
Okay.
♪ 我不记得我说了什么... ♪
♪ I can't remember what I said... ♪
我们可以去看春季比赛
We could watch the spring game.
是的，达科塔是个橄榄球迷
Yeah, Dakota's a football fanatic.
嗯，不是，不是球迷，亲爱的
Well, not a, not a fanatic, honey.
是个天才
A phenom.
哦，对不起，宝贝 天才
Oh, sorry, baby. Phenom.
他是个天才
He's a phenom.
你知道，他进入了ESPN的50强
You know, he made ESPN's top 50.
- 是吗？ - 嗯哼
- Is that so? - Mm-hmm.
你选好学校了吗？
Did you pick a school yet?
呃，阿拉巴马大学
Uh, Alabama.
离理工大学有点远，不是吗？
Little far from Tech, isn't it?
嗯，我申请了阿拉巴马大学
Well, I applied to Alabama
就在达科塔接受他们录取通知后
as soon as Dakota accepted their offer.
那可是所很难进的学校
It's just a tough school to get into.
呃，但是，你知道，我和萨班教练谈过，
Uh, but I, you know, I talked to Coach Saban,
告诉他我有多么希望她去那里
told him how much,I wanted her there.
当她看着我的时候，我发挥得更好
I play better when she's watching me.
你知道，萨班教练退休了，对吧？
You know,Coach Saban retired, right?
什么？
What?
- 呃...不 不  - 他退休了吗？
- Uh... no. No. - Did he retire?
那是谣言
That's rumors.
你知道，也许我们应该去看这场比赛
You know, maybe we should go to this game.
- 你和他谈过了？ - 是的，是的 他--
- Did you talk to him? - Yeah, yeah. He--
是的，我们去看比赛吧
Yeah, let's go to the game.
♪ 第二天，因为没有休息... ♪
♪ The next day, 'cause there ain't no rest... ♪
上！上！上！上！
Go! Go! Go! Go!
开球！
Hike!
那个狗娘养的可是个名人
That son of a bitch is a celebrity.
如果我进不了阿拉巴马大学，
If I don't get into Alabama,
我会死的，爸爸
I'm gonna die, Daddy.
我向上帝发誓，我会死的
I swear to God, I'm gonna die.
你不会死的
You're not gonna die.
我会死的
I'll die.
你们俩在做爱吗？
Are you two having sex?
爸爸
Daddy.
- 好吧，我得问问  - 当然
- Well, I had to ask. - Of course.
这就是我问的结果
And that's what I get for asking.
你们有做好安全措施吗？
Are you being careful?
我们有规矩，我们也遵守
We have a rule and we stick to it.
我肯定会后悔问你这个问题，
I'm gonna regret asking you this,
但这条规矩是什么？
but what is this rule?
只要他不射在我里面，
As long as he never comes in me,
他可以射在我身上的任何地方
he can come anywhere on me.
我去买瓶胡椒博士 你要什么吗？
I'm gonna go get a Dr. Pepper. You want anything?
不用
No.
谢谢你这么通情达理，爸爸
Thanks for being so cool, Daddy.
这种事我永远不会告诉妈妈
I could never tell Mama these kind of things.
能给我来瓶胡椒博士吗？ - 可以
Can I get a Dr. Pepper? - Yes.
你后面有波旁威士忌吗？
You got any bourbon back there?
先生？
Sir?
算了
Never mind.
- 今天过得不好？ - 可以这么说
- Rough day? - You could say that.
我有一些大麻软糖
如果你想要的话 免费的
I got some pot gummies if you want. No charge.
哦，你真是太好了，亲爱的，
Oh, that's real sweet of you, honey,
但我想，我还是算了吧
but I think,I'm gonna pass on that.
我欠你多少钱？
How much do I owe you?
四块
That'll be four, please.
四块？
Four?
给你 不用找了
There you go. And keep that for yourself.
谢谢
Appreciate it.
你好
Hello.
他活下来了
He survived.
他怎么样？
How'd he do?
很菜，非常菜
Green, real green.
但别说不行，而且他还努力了
but don't say no, and he tries.
我是说，这还不错
I mean, that's something.
如果你问我
那就是浪费大学学位
Waste of a college degree, if you ask me.
好吧，没人问你 也没人问我
Well, nobody's asking you. Nobody's asking me, either.
有其父必有其子，你懂我的意思吧
Like father like son, if you know what I mean.
没人比我更懂了
No one knows better.
我有一大堆“有其父必有其子”的例子
I got a truckload of "father like son."
所以我才把他交给你，
That's why I put him with you,
让他别惹麻烦
to keep him out of trouble.
- 我会尽力而为  - 好吧
- I'll do my best. - All right.
我晚点再跟你谈
I'll talk to you later.
你特么在逗我吗？
这个漂亮的小杂种
Are you shitting me? This pretty son of a bitch
把手放在我女儿屁股上？
with his giant hand on my daughter's ass?
- 你刚才说什么？ - 什么？
- What did you just say? - What?
你说的是我的屁股？
Are you talking about my ass?
不，我说的是那家伙
抓了我女儿的屁股
No, I'm talking about that guy grabbing my daughter's ass
在全世界面前
in front of the whole world.
哦，我的天哪，那是达科塔·洛文
Oh, my gosh, that's Dakota Loving.
你一定是在耍我
You've got to be shitting me.
库珀
Cooper.
这是你的舱位
This is your pod.
嘿，呃，你晚饭吃什么？
Hey, uh, what you got going on for supper?
我-我不知道
I-I don't know.
你里面有吃的吗？
You got food in there?
我可能会开车回镇上
I'll probably just drive back to town.
关门
Close the door.
谢谢
Thank you.
说“谢谢”
Say "gracias."
谢谢 （Gracias.）
Gracias.
你需要学西班牙语
You need to learn Spanish
因为我他妈的不会整天说英语
'cause I'm not speaking,English all fucking day.
- 好吧  - 好吗？
- Okay. - All right?
这是“啤酒”
This is "cerveza."
是的，啤酒     我知道啤酒
Yes. Cerveza. I know cerveza.
好吧，好吧 烤架
All right, all right. Parrilla.
- 烤架  - 是的，那是肉
- Parrilla. - Yeah, and that's carne.
- 肉 - 是的
- Carne. - Yeah.
当你-当你喝啤酒的时候，
And when-when you're drinking a beer,
你说，“我正在喝啤酒”
you say, "Estoy tomando una cerveza."
“我-我正在喝啤酒”？
"Estoy t-tomando una cerveza"?
当你吃玉米卷的时候，你说，
And when you're eating a taco, you say,
“我正在吃一个装满鸡巴的玉米卷”
"Estoy comiendo un taco lleno de verga."
-“我正在……”，不，不，不
-"Estoy...",No, no, no.
- 不要那样说  - 不……
- Don't say that. - No...
好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
你就说，“我正在吃玉米卷”
You just say, "Estoy comiendo un taco."
- 我正在吃玉米卷  - 好吧，你懂了
- Estoy comiendo un taco. - Okay, you got it.
你知道，如果我用英语问你什么，
And you know, if I ask you something in English,
就问我用西班牙语怎么说
just ask me how to say it in Spanish
一个月后你就会说两种语言了
and you'll be bilingual in a month.
- 好吧  - 好吧
- Okay. - All right.
接一下
Get that.
嗯，我的意思是，她只是想和你谈谈
Well, I mean, she just wants to talk to you.
她是你的女儿
She's your daughter.
你好，小宝贝
Hola, chiquita.
你好
Hello.
那是我女儿
That was my daughter.
我妻子不让她做某件事，
My wife told her no about something,
而且她知道我在老板面前
说不上话，所以...
and she knows that I have no pull with the boss, so...
那么，埃尔维奥，他是你儿子？
So, Elvio, he's your son?
赫曼尼托
Hermanito.
呃，他，呃，他是我弟弟
Uh, it-- uh, he's my little brother.
好的 所以，你全家都在地里干活？
Okay. So, your whole family works the patch?
所有人的家人都在地里干活
Everybody's whole family works the patch.
嘿
Hey.
我叔叔在监狱里待了十年
My uncle was in prison for ten years.
- 真的吗？
- Really?
伙计，一个重罪犯
想赚六位数的唯一方法
Dude, the o-- the only way for a felon to make six figures
就是偷或者在地里干活
is to steal it or work the patch.
我试过偷，结果
我跟他落得一样的下场
I tried to steal it, and,I ended up right where he was.
不过，你知道吗？
You know what, though?
你真正努力工作更好
It's better you work for it real hard.
你知道吗？这样，就没人能把它夺走
You know? That way, nobody can take it away.
我能理解
I can see that.
比如，埃尔维奥，他很聪明
你知道吗？真的很聪明
Like, Elvio, he's smart, you know? Real smart.
他没进监狱，直接来地里干活
He skipped prison and went straight to the patch.
拥有自己的房子
Owns his home.
卡车也还清了贷款 妻子不用工作
Got his truck paid off. Wife don't work.
我的意思是
有多少个24岁的年轻人能做到这样？
I mean, how many 24-year-olds can say that?
- 没几个  - 没几个
- Not very many. - Not very many.
哦，对了，肉好了
Oh, yeah, the meat's ready.
好了，我得走了，宝贝
Okay, I got to go, baby.
意思是“我们去吃饭吧”
That means, "Let's go eat."
好的，好的
Okay, okay.
嘿，把我的啤酒拿来
Hey, bring my beer.
吃吧，伙计
Dig in, man.
用西班牙语怎么说？
How do you say that in Spanish?
不太会说，但是，呃，
Not really, but, uh,
这样就行了
that'll work.
哦，伙计，真好吃
Oh, man, that's good.
- 好吃，对吧？ 嗯哼
- Good, right? Mm-hmm.
我靠，真辣
Holy shit, that's hot.
你还差得远呢，孩子
You got a way to go, son.
这还不是最辣的，兄弟
That's not even the hot one, bro.
这还不是最辣的？
How is that not the hot one?
没那么糟，兄弟 你给他吃了什么？
It's not that bad, bro. What'd you give him?
两个屌辣椒
Dos tacos de verga.
你还好吗，孩子？
You okay, son?
- 没事 别他妈的死在这儿
- Yeah. Don't fucking die here.
我靠
Holy shit.
哥们，喝点啤酒，兄弟 你还好吗？
Man, drink some beer, bro. You good?
好了，我要去睡了
All right, I'm turning in.
- 晚安，爸爸
- 不，不 你跟我来
- Good night, Daddy. - No, no. You're coming with me.
- 什么？ - 没错
- What? That's right.
我们要像你九岁时那样，
We're gonna have an old-fashioned sleep-in,
睡个懒觉
like we used to when you were nine.
我才不要和爸爸睡同一张床
I'm not sleeping in the same bed as my father.
你睡床上 我睡地板上
You sleep in the bed. I'll sleep on the floor.
就在门正前的那块地板上
The part of the floor that's directly in front of the door.
呃，我的房间在哪儿，诺里斯先生？
Uh, where's my room, Mr. Norris?
哦，我们给你安排了小型套房，
Oh, we put you in the junior suite,
就是这张该死的沙发
which is this fucking couch here.
做个好梦 来吧，宝贝
Sweet dreams. Come on, baby.
你并没有阻止任何事情，爸爸
You're not preventing anything, Daddy.
只是推迟了而已
Just postponing it.
你只是让紧张的气氛进一步加剧
You're just forcing the tension to rise even further.
你知道，我无法预料
当他最终和我单独相处时，
You know, there is no telling what I'll let him do to me
我会让他对我做什么
when he finally has me alone.
你知道，你时不时会说一些话，
You know, every now and then, you say things
让人想起你基因库的另一面
that harken back the other side of your gene pool.
- 你在侮辱妈妈吗？ - 是的
- Are you insulting Mama? - Yeah, I am.
你不认为我们会长久，对吧？
You don't think we're gonna last, do you?
那件运动衫有配套的裤子吗？
Did that sweatshirt come with pants?
就像一套的那种？
Like as a set?
我觉得那像是养老院穿的
I think that's just for nursing homes.
我爱他
I love him.
亲爱的，你经历的每一段恋爱关系
Honey, every romantic relationship
都会失败，
you'll ever have will be a failure,
除了最后一段
except the last one.
你认为这是你最后一段恋爱关系
Do you think this is the last relationship
了吗？
you're ever gonna have?
我希望是
I want it to be.
好吧，见鬼，我们都希望每一段都是
Well, hell, we want all of them to be.
你认为会是最后一段吗？
Do you think it will be?
他可以拥有任何人
He can have anyone.
- 好吧，该死，你也可以  - 爸爸
- Well, shit, you can, too. - Daddy.
按照你的逻辑
我现在就应该和他分手，
By your logic, I should just break up with him now
免得自己受苦，
and spare myself the suffering
直接等待最后一段
and just wait for the last one.
不是那样的
It don't work that way.
你得在失败中学会爱
You got to love your way through the failures.
不到最后，你永远不知道
是不是最后一次
You never know if you're in the last one till you're in it.
你以为和你妈是最后一次吗？
Did you think Mama was the last one?
当然不是
Shit, no.
宝贝，说真的，我和你妈
能维持六个星期，我都震惊了
Hell, honey, I was shocked your mom and I lasted six weeks.
那为什么持续了那么久？
Well, why did it last so long?
和你一样
Same as you.
虽然我们彼此都不合适，
I mean, as wrong as we were for each other,
但我爱她
I-I loved her.
我对她爱不释手
Couldn't keep my damn hands off of her.
该死，我仍然爱她
Shit, I still love her.
如果她失语了，我明天就再娶她一次
If she lost the power of speech, I'd marry her again tomorrow.
我从未和他睡过
I've never slept with him.
我们几乎在
所有能做的地方都做过爱
We've had sex just about everywhere you can do it.
亲爱的……
Honey...
我从未和他睡过
I've never slept with him.
就像，我……
Like, I've...
就像，我从未在他怀里睡着过，或者……
Like, I've never fallen asleep in his arms or...
在他怀里醒来过
like, woken up in them.
爸爸，如果我保证不做爱，
Daddy, if I promise not to have sex,
我能和他一起睡在沙发上吗？
can I just sleep with him on the couch?
求你了？
Please?
只是睡觉？
Just sleep?
- 你保证？ - 嗯哼
- You promise? - Mm-hmm.
我保证 嗯哼
I do. Mm-hmm.
那沙发是租的
That couch is a rental.
好的 知道了
Okay. Got it.
天哪，我的蛋蛋去哪儿了？
Lord, where'd my nuts go?
你怎么做到的？
How'd you pull this off?
- 我做了个承诺  - 嗯，是吗？什么承诺？
- I made a promise. - Mm, yeah? What's the promise.
我可以和你一起睡
但我们不能做爱
Well, I can sleep with you, but we can't have sex.
你能保证吗？
Can you make that promise?
呃……
Uh...
我宁愿不保证
I'd rather not.
我知道，宝贝，但你能保证吗？
Well, I know baby, but can you make it?
嗯
Mm.
我们可以，我们可以摩擦吗？
Can we, can we dry hump?
你可以抱着我
You can hold me.
好吧，我们来谈谈这个
Okay, well, let's talk about this.
你保证不做爱
I mean, you promised no sex.
那……那排除了很多东西
Well, that... that leaves out a lot.
-喂？
- Yeah?
发生了什么事？
What happened?
看来他不是最后一个
Guess he's not the last one.
他不知道自己错过了什么
He don't know what he's missing.
来吧，宝贝
Come on, babe.
来吧，宝贝，躺下
Come on, babe, lay down.
过来，亲爱的 过来
Come here, honey. Come here.
你怎么总是对的？
How come you're always right?
因为我这辈子都在犯错
'Cause I spent all my life being wrong.
我从未忘记那些教训
I never forgot the lessons.
谢谢你
Thank you.
亲爱的
Honey.
该死的阿拉巴马
Fuck Alabama.
是啊 去死吧
Yeah. Fuck 'em.
嘿，18寸的太小了 换24寸的
Hey, the 18's too small. Go to 24.
库珀，去拿24英寸的管钳
Cooper, go get the 24-inch pipe wrench.
哪个是？
Which one is that?
写着“24”的那个
The one that says "24."
快去！
Go!
跟你胳膊一样粗的那个 你会看到的
The one the size of your arm. You'll see it.
- 你找到了吗？
- You got it?
- 我正在找 快点！
- I'm looking. Hurry up!
他拿着24寸的来了  - 我搞定了
He's bringing the 24. - I got this.
他在干什么？好了，开始吧
What is he doing? Okay, here we go.
我找到了
I got it.
他拿着24寸的来了
He's bringing the 24.
好了，就应该是这样
Okay, that's what it should've been.
哦，耶 我们来了
Oh, yeah. Here we come.
哇！
Whoa!